[
  {
    "question": "What is important for getting a good object-oriented design?",
    "answers": [0, 1, 2, 3],
    "options": [
      "Abstraction/generalization",
      "Delegation",
      "Loose coupling",
      "High cohesion"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Important keywords related to the description of a design pattern are...",
    "answers": [0, 1, 3],
    "options": ["Context", "Problem", "Programming language", "Solution"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Description of patterns specific to a programming language is called..",
    "answers": [2],
    "options": ["Architectural pattern", "Design pattern", "Idioms", "Tactics"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Description of fundamental structural organisation or schema for software systems is called...",
    "answers": [0],
    "options": ["Architectural pattern", "Design pattern", "Idioms", "Tactics"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of pattern is the Singleton pattern?",
    "answers": [2],
    "options": ["Additional", "Behavioral", "Creational", "Structural"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of pattern is the Observer pattern?",
    "answers": [1],
    "options": ["Additional", "Behavioral", "Creational", "Structural"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of pattern is the Composite pattern?",
    "answers": [3],
    "options": ["Additional", "Behavioral", "Creational", "Structural"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of pattern is the Factory pattern?",
    "answers": [2],
    "options": ["Additional", "Behavioral", "Creational", "Structural"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of pattern is the Strategy pattern?",
    "answers": [1],
    "options": ["Additional", "Behavioral", "Creational", "Structural"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of pattern is the Proxy pattern?",
    "answers": [3],
    "options": ["Additional", "Behavioral", "Creational", "Structural"]
  }
]
